get it.
>> I will work on that intro. Uh,
uh, comedian of the night. Now, I know
that I've forgotten it for the past
couple weeks, but we have a special
situation. We have a special guest in
the house, Jose Raymond from doing his
Watts to Hawaii tour. [cheering]
He'll be at uh, the Playground September
4th, I believe. That's a Friday night.
Uh, comedian of the night tonight.
You're earning yourself a five minute
spot on that show. So, dress up, look
nice, and try hard tonight. Okay, work
it. Work it. Try to get that spot. I'm
gonna put the sauce back here for
incentive. Um, oh, tonight's theme, the
best part. Okay, so every week we do a
theme. Sometimes it's like jokes out of
a hat where you pull a topic and you
figure it out. Sometimes it's crowd work
where we interact with each other.
Tonight is a type of crowd work. It's
the most dangerous type of crowd crowd
work. It's actually the most dangerous
type of comedy. Ladies and gentlemen,
tonight is heckle night.
>> Ooh, I felt the the the air leave and
come back to the room. So, those of you
that do not know what Heckle Knight is,
normally it is frowned upon when an
audience member interacts negatively
with a comedian. However, the Comedy
Simulator is all about our comedians
getting training. So, sometimes we pull
out this cartridge of the simulator and
we plug it in. Now, this comes with a
disclaimer.
This will raise your blood pressure if
you interact it. You won't be able to
help but feel like the simulator feels
real. And the same goes for our comics,
too. So this is two-part audience for
audience or two-part uh advice from
audience and comedians. This is a
simulation.
We are using this for training purposes.
If you interact with a comedian, they
will interact with you and that's how it
happens. Don't take it personally. Just
know that everything is said in the
intent of humor. That is the point. If
you are brought into an interaction that
you do not want to be a part of, simply
put an X with your arms in front of your
chest and the comedian will know that
you are not to be interacted with.
However, if you were the heckler,
you no longer have that right and the
comedian will continue to heckle and go
back and forth, right? Because if you if
you throw a shot and then run away,
you're an [ __ ] and we will make sure
that doesn't happen. So, just so you
know, if you do interact, the interact
will be back and forth. Nobody gets to
say when that stops, but remember it's a
simulation. If at any point you you feel
uncomfortable, let me know. Or feel free
to go off for air for a second, too.
Separate yourself from the room. That's
okay. Remember, it is a simulation.
Also, one rule, one heckler at a time.
When the whole room dog piles, it
becomes impossible. So, one person at a
time, unless you got the Holy Ghost in
you and it just says the right thing in
the right moment, then amen. Let it out.
Exercise that. I I'm cool with that. But
we try to do one at a time. and keep it
fair. Sound good, everybody?
[applause]
>> Awesome. I like to hear that. So, don't
be afraid to heckle our comics tonight.
Uh, comedians, remember once again, this
is a simulation. Don't take this
personally. Nobody hates your art. They
just found something about you to make
fun of. All right, that's all that
means. Maybe be less make fun of. All
right, that begin that that concludes
the entry speech. Are we ready to begin
the comedy simulator? [applause]
Cuz once we begin the simulation, it
goes until it's over. Are we ready to
begin simulation?
Let's do it. The heck is heckle
simulation begins? Begin simulator. So,
I'm just going to start [music] doing
um so I recently got a air purifier in
my house because my air is dirty, or so
I've been told. Uh and I found out that
it has a color coding system. It's blue
if your air is clean. It's yellow if
your air is dirty. And it's red if your
air is [ __ ] gross, right? So, I plug
it in. It's running blue. I'm feeling
good about things. My girlfriend's
asleep and I'm like,
"Can this thing tell if I fart?"
A simple seven-year-old thought. Will
this air purifier detect my fart? So, I
let one loose across the room and 7
seconds later, it went from blue to
orange, and I start dying laughing. The
child in me starts letting loose the
laughter and then it turns red and now I
have a consideration.
Did I really just mess up my air that
much to red? Like California wildfires,
do they get orange? Like how bad is red?
Like give me a scale here. Like what did
I just do to my purifier? Did I
unpurify?
>> Yeah, right. It's a carbon filter.
Hopefully it caught all that. Um,
>> what's in that hot sauce? [laughter]
>> What's in the hot sauce? It's uh fart
ammunition. Apparently, that's what it
is. It is prefarts. It's bottles of
prefarts. Once once just add person
enzymes and it's got everything you
need.
>> Just add stomach probiotic and you got
everything you need. Yes, Dove.
>> I'm wondering if the purifier all that.
>> Yeah. Okay. I just want to heckle you
for heckling by raising your hand. What
the [ __ ] was that? [laughter]
This is supposed to be re rude. And
you're like, "Excuse me, sir. I have an
interjection if I may."
>> I have a a quit proquo. [laughter]
I like that. That was like felt like a
negotiation. Uh
>> dirty air is just a fart.
>> Dirty air is just a fart.
So you're saying that all dirty air is
farts? You know, at a certain point, we
live in an ozone. We're just ancestrally
breathing in
the farts of like the 1200s. You ever
think about that? Like it's just like
the water table, right? The water table
never leaves the planet. We're drinking
Julia Caesar's piss probably, right? You
ever think you might be breathing his
farts? Nobody ever thought of that.
Nobody thought of that.
That's that's that's funny about thing
about leadership is that we think our
leaders know what's going on. I got a
good example for you. One Caesar thought
that wine was stupid and it made you an
idiot and that you should only drink
orange juice. So, there was a Caesar
that only drank orange juice. His name
was Orange Julius. No, I'm joking. It
wasn't. [laughter] Don't [ __ ] believe
everything I say. I'm not a leader.
Nobody was drinking nothing but orange
juice. Watched everybody drink wine.
Spent his life drinking orange juice.
Died at 28. Kidney stones. That dude was
wrong as [ __ ] Just because you get the
seat of power doesn't mean you're smart,
right? That's what that means. Um,
little history lesson. Don't know where
that came from. That's part of my
trauma. Uh, I just regurgitate facts.
So, I think you like me. That's what I
That's all I want, right? A little
shirt. You get it? Uh,
>> all right. Anybody else want to heckle
or should I just bring up the first
comic? You guys ready to get more comics
going?
>> Yeah.
>> All right. So, we have a number one slot
open.
Would anybody like to just Jose? Ladies
and gentlemen, the headliner watch the
Hawaii tour coming soon to a stage near
you. Gifting out a 5minute set the comic
of the night. Get ready for Jose
Raymond.
[cheering]
[applause]
>> Keep clapping. KEEP CLAPPING. EVERYBODY
CLAP. COME ON.
>> CLAP. There you go. [applause] I'm
specifically talking to the table of uh
Indians. I'm going to call you guys
Indians. Yes, you guys are Indians.
>> Yes. All right. You guys are polite as
[ __ ] Say something back.
You guys are good. Everybody's good.
>> Laugh at this [ __ ] You [ __ ]
are holding in. It's a free show. LAUGH.
>> Comedians have a good time. I'm just
here to promote the show. Uh the
comedians are coming up here. Do do a
spot. Best comic night gets five minutes
at the playground on Friday. We're at
like about 180 180 almost 200 tickets
sold right now. So you guys going to
have a nice crowd. Hopefully they're
better than these [ __ ]
Um, and I only call you [ __ ]
cuz I don't know your name individually.
[laughter] You guys laugh at this [ __ ]
Comedy is hard as [ __ ] When I I used to
be illegal and I had to tell my mom that
I was going to quit seven of my jobs to
do comedy.
And you guys don't laugh at this [ __ ]
That's crazy.
>> My mom comes to my shows. She like, "I
told you [ __ ] to keep at least
three of those jobs." [laughter]
This why I smoke a lot of weed. If you
don't smoke weed, smoke it. I smoke a
lot of weed cuz you guys are not going
to hurt my feelings when you guys don't
laugh at my jokes. I still hear
laughter.
You're smiling, bro. Laugh. If you
smoked weed, you'll be laughing at this
[ __ ]
Any tourists here other than the Indians
right there?
No. Learn some [ __ ] If you're in
Hawaii, man, I learned a lot of [ __ ]
being here. Originally from LA. Grew up
in a black and Mexican neighborhood. I
didn't know that there were other
ethnicities, you know, like I got
exposed here in Hawaii. I didn't know
that Filipinos were a thing. Like, I
didn't know that Filipinos existed
till I moved to Hawaii. The first time I
saw a Filipino
cuz they look Mexican, right? But I was
confused. First time I saw a Filipino, I
was like, "That's got to be a slow
Mexican." That is
cuz Filipinos look Mexican except for
their eyes. cuz you know when you cover
their eyes like
I remember I COVERED A DUDE'S EYES. I
was like yo you look Mexican except
you got a little down syndrome in your
eyes man
they're LIKE NO HE'S FILIPINO LIKE oh
[laughter]
I don't know what that means but
I remember we were speaking to him in
Spanish and he kept speaking Talog and I
never heard these sounds so I thought he
was really slow. I [ __ ] bought him
lunch and [ __ ] [laughter]
We been good friends. I take him for ice
cream every Friday. A
>> and he gives me ponet.
>> So anyways, you guys get a lose. Laugh
at this [ __ ]
>> I'm going through my second divorce.
>> Yeah. Clap.
>> And it's it's hard out here with this
[ __ ] sexual climate. Everybody
>> it's [ __ ] weird nowadays, man. Damn.
And there's this question everybody asks
men, especially men. We we ask this
question. Are you a tits man or an ass
man? That's a big question everybody
wants to know. You guys heard this,
right, fellas?
>> No.
>> You like tits or you like ass? I think
in 2026,
>> the real answer, the only answer is I'm
a vagina man.
>> Cuz there's a lot of [ __ ] that
have tits. What is that?
>> You're in your second divorce.
>> I am on my second divorce and this why
I'm getting to know.
>> No. Uh, [ __ ] I smoke a lot of weed and
you just heckle. I forgot this was a
heckling show.
I thought my ex-wife sent you, [ __ ]
[laughter]
>> This is my second divor. I don't want to
get into what my second divorce is
happening, but it's happening. This is
why I'm here drinking to forget about
that [ __ ] And you want to talk about
it?
I'll tell you why I got divorced the
first time, man. I was illegal. And the
easiest way to get your [ __ ] together is
to get married. and I got married, but
we both didn't know, my wife at the time
and myself, that we were both illegal.
>> So, I had to get divorced. [laughter]
You good? Are you white?
>> I don't know. I can't see myself.
[laughter]
>> You look white, man. I talk I talk [ __ ]
to a lot of white people nowadays since
I became a citizen.
got new confidence
cuz they can't call nobody on me no
more, man. And I don't I don't care
about anybody's politics
at all. I don't give a [ __ ] Call
immigration if you want. They're going
to be practicing
as soon as you call them. As soon as
immigration shows up, all I say is I
pledge allegiance to the flag.
And they kind of let me go.
Anyways, that's my time, you guys. Uh
thank you very much.
>> [applause]
>> I wanted to take the bullet cuz as a
comedian the bullet is hard to [ __ ]
do and I've been uh doing comedy for a
while man. Give it up for Chino. Always
[ __ ] have a platform in Maui.
[applause and cheering]
I tried that [ __ ] I tried doing I
travel all over now and I tried doing
comedy here like every [ __ ] week and
it's hard as [ __ ] And Chino has figured
out a way to give comedians here a
platform. So thank you Cheto. My name is
Jose Raymond. [applause] Appreciate you
guys. We'll be at the playground Friday.
Thanks.
>> Hey, check out Jose Raymond this Friday
over at the playground September 4th.
[applause]
>> Headlining from Watch to Hawaii. Dude,
me and that guy go way back. I've known
him since I was like 12 years old. 13
years old. Yeah, right. We go way back.
That's true.
>> Yeah. His uncle used to [ __ ] my aunt.
That's how that works. [laughter]
>> And me. [laughter]
>> Okay. Why?
>> I was taller than his uncle at 13. What
are you talking about, dude?
>> How you going to bottom for somebody
shorter than you? That doesn't make
sense, right?
>> He's got to put a pillow under my hips
if that's the case. We got to figure out
his hip differential, right?
>> That's That's off. Uh Daniel, you'll go
uh you're on deck. Um cuz Rick's already
So here, ladies and gentlemen, in the
number two spot, normally our one spot,
but we left it open. You know him,
Maui's biggest drug dealer, RICK JAGGER.
>> [cheering and applause]
>> ALL RIGHT. HOW WE DOING, GUYS? Keep it
going for Chino.
>> All right. Uh
[ __ ] So, football's getting ready to
start. Y'all excited?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Is it just me or does
football start way too [ __ ] early
over here?
It's just hard to get excited about
drinking a beer
>> when you have to eat some uh
>> Captain Crunch before.
>> Yeah,
>> there's something fundamentally wrong if
you have to set an alarm to wake up to
watch football.
>> Yeah,
>> I I
it's just too too [ __ ] early.
Uh
so I grew up in a a family of eight and
uh my dad was the only one who was
allowed to fart without leaving the
room.
The rest of the family had to go to the
either to the bathroom or your room, but
you couldn't do it you couldn't do it at
the table. you couldn't do it watching
TV.
And uh so my dad would be sitting around
watching TV and he'd catch a whiff of
something. [snorts] And he say uh oh, he
called it bombing, too. I don't know if
that's a Navy thing or or what. He
didn't call it farting. He called it
bombing. So, we'd be sitting around
watching TV and he'd get a whiff of
something and uh it could have even been
one of his farts, but uh he'd say, "Is
that you bombing over there, Ricky?"
>> Don't blame it on Lucky.
Lucky was the name of my uh big sister.
[laughter]
>> No, Lucky was our dog. And uh but uh
if he caught you, you know, you you had
to be excused for the rest of the night.
You couldn't watch TV. You couldn't do
[ __ ]
This is just to say that my dad was an
So,
uh but he did take us on vacation once
in a while. Uh so he's not all bad. Uh
we were on vacation when I was about 13
and we were somewhere in North Carolina
and he got he got caught uh he got he
got lost going back to the campground
and we ended up in front of this
drive-in movie theater
and all that was on the marquee was a
name of a movie and a time. So, it was
like The Wild Ones 8:00, new sheriff in
town, 10:00.
There were no ratings or any other
information on this marquee.
>> So, we pulled around,
paid the guy, and we pulled around, put
the speaker on the window, and they
started to run the coming attractions.
Right
now, the very first preview they showed
was for a movie called Deep Throat.
>> [snorts]
>> Yes, you got it. My dad had mistakenly
driven his entire family to the porno
drive-in.
As soon as the preview started, my mom
is like, "Tom, start the car. We're
leaving." Meanwhile, my brother and I
are hanging our heads out the window,
trying to get a better look. Because up
until this point, the only naked ladies
I had ever seen were in the pages of
magazines back at my friend's house. But
these ladies were alive and moving
around and doing things I had never seen
before. Not only that, they were huge.
They were 30 FEET TALL.
You know, for the few minutes it took us
to turn around and get out of there, my
dad had become my greatest hero. Thanks,
Dad.
All right. Uh,
I've been a pharmacist now for 42 years,
guys.
Uh lately I've been doing a lot of
contract work because for some reason
they really don't like to hire a
65year-old
pharmacist.
>> What was I talking about?
>> Oh yeah. I got uh interviewing. I really
hate interviewing. I hate that whole
process. I do okay with the interview
till they get to the question. So, where
do you see yourself in 5 years?
I'm like surfing on Maui.
Can you help me with that?
Yeah, I didn't get that job. Don't get
me wrong, pharmacy has been very good to
me. It's given me a great life. It's
allowed me to travel. It brought me
here. I'm just really, really tired
of always working with drugs.
>> And now
I just want to do some. Okay,
>> thanks guys. My name's Rick Jagger.
[applause]
>> Rick Jagger, ladies and gentlemen, he
wants to do drugs now.
>> Well, have you come to the right town?
[laughter]
What do you want? Uh,
>> no. Rick Rick's turned a drinking game
out of our comment section. Uh, they're
all drinking Jagger bombs during a set.
I don't know why. Uh, so speaking of our
live stream, this is live streaming
currently on YouTube right now as we
speak. Check out our channel @ comedy
simulator. Join the comment section if
you think you guys are heckling. You're
not. They are heckling us horribly right
now. You should check out the comment
section. They are always roasting us.
But sometimes they get free bottles of
hot sauce. I've given to some of the
people on there. So, keep checking in.
Keep talking [ __ ] We appreciate you.
Like and subscribe so that we can make
money off of you being mean to us. All
right. Keeping this moving right along.
You guys ready for some more comedy?
>> Coming to the stage, one of my favorite
people on the planet. We play golf all
the time. Check out his stroke. Get up
for Dance, Ste.
[applause]
>> Keep it stroking for me.
>> That's right. Jumping right into it. All
right, let's keep it going for Chino.
[applause]
>> Another man with a lovely stroke.
Give it up for the bar staff.
[applause]
>> I don't think I've ever seen champagne
on tap before.
>> This is a fancy place.
>> I'm not roasting you guys.
It's all good.
>> But thank you guys for coming out. All
right, Rick brings up a good topic
because he is one of the functional drug
dealers on this island.
like finding a a good worthy dealer
here. It's like if the dating scene is
similar, you guys are going through hell
right now. You're getting ghosted a lot.
We need customer service.
Like, who do you call
>> when your dealer doesn't show?
>> You can always call Ghostbusters, do
stuff.
I don't know. Yes. Question in the back.
This is interesting. Yeah. The only dude
holding up his hand already.
>> What?
>> Yes, I know. Jose,
>> you're you're calling him right now.
>> No, you can't. Who do you call? You said
who do you call?
>> Who do you call? Hey, Jose.
>> Call the Ghostbusters.
>> Great.
>> Where are you guys visiting from?
>> Yeah, you.
>> Me
>> in the front? Yes,
>> I live here.
>> Okay, fantastic. Where are you living
here?
>> Pukalani.
>> Pukalani. All right. How long you been
here?
>> Three months.
>> Three months. Man, you're almost local.
>> I know.
>> Jeez, you're almost there. Just add
seven years.
>> It's all good. Hey, welcome. What do you
do?
>> Oh, uh, I'm a therapist for kids
>> there. Okay. Fixing them or making them
worse?
>> Fixing.
>> Okay, good. How's the best way to fix a
kid?
>> Fix dad.
>> Right. I Yeah, I'm working. Yeah. Help
me.
>> Yeah. No, you're going to have to pay me
a lot of money for that.
>> Give her money, Dan.
>> Sure. Yeah. You take Venmo.
>> I like you.
>> Hey, Jimbo. Give her money for me.
>> No, it doesn't work that way. You got
>> Well, as long as you're getting the
money. You're getting You're getting
picky here.
>> I want you to earn it.
>> Hey,
>> wait. That's how you make the money.
>> All right. I Yeah, by you.
You can have Wait, her money or or
>> money for this?
>> Money for this? Yeah. You get You Hey,
dude. I'll give you twice what you paid
to get in.
>> You just got it in your pocket.
>> I know, right? You guys are so nice.
You're polite.
>> Thank you.
>> Yeah, you are. You're lovely.
>> Cowboy hat. I got to talk to you.
>> I know. You haven't heckled yet,
>> but I love your hat.
>> Thank you.
>> I'm pro cowboy hat. Where are you guys
from?
>> I'm not going to believe this. NEW YORK
CITY. NEW YORK CITY.
>> God damn.
>> You want one of them New York cowpokes?
>> Well, it's true, but I I did grow up in
Texas and I I wear the hat in New York
more than Texas.
>> All right. All right. You got boots on,
too?
>> No, not in a not not walking the
streets.
>> Ask the shoes.
>> What? What are your shoes?
>> I'm wearing Vans.
>> Vans. All right.
>> Honestly, what year?
>> I don't know. 2008. 2008.
>> All right. All right. All right, we're
learning about him. How What's your
name, by the way?
>> Gavin.
>> Gavin. Gavin. Oh, man. Gavin's really
taking a hit.
>> Oh, man. I like you, Gavin. Love the
hat. I don't know. But yeah, as you can
tell by this, I'm definitely going
through a midlife crisis.
[laughter]
But I've been having those since I was
15. So, like, as long as I keep breaking
down, I'm never going to die. I think I
think I found a cheat code.
>> Oh my god, I'm having a crisis every
day. Right now, it's just on stage.
>> I don't know. You guys are fun. I
haven't even had to look at any notes.
>> Oh man.
[laughter]
>> You're doing great.
>> A Thank you.
>> You're a polite heckler. You're helping
those kids. That's true. That is true.
>> What's your dreams? I believe in you.
>> A All right, everybody. All right,
please say that louder. This is for
everyone tonight. You need this and you
didn't get it.
>> 1 2 3.
>> I believe in you.
>> There you go. [applause] The most
positive heckle night, man. We can't go
down from here. All right. My name is
Dan Stevie. I love y'all. [applause]
Dan Stevie, ladies and gentlemen,
>> okay.
>> Hey, he asked one poignant question.
What's the fastest way to fix a kid?
That is a very good question. Dan,
you're a father of three. You know the
answer. You don't fix them, you make
another one. You just make another one
>> and you hope they become the success.
And you got
>> Oh, spoken like a middle child. Yeah,
right. I got you. Sorry about that. I
didn't mean to do that. All right,
ladies and gentlemen, coming up next to
the stage runs the Tuesday night mic in
Kihei. Whoa, what just happened there?
Was there a sound switch?
>> It's getting in
>> or did my ear just unclog? What was that
that just happened?
>> Okay, sorry. It must have been my ear.
I've been waiting for that thing to
plug. All right. Anyways, coming up next
on stage runs the Tuesday night show
every Tuesday in Kihei. If this isn't
enough standup comedy for you, uh, open
mic style. I don't know why you would
need more, but if you need more, every
Tuesday in Kihei, check them out. Ladies
and gentlemen, Morgan Tam Asian.
[applause]
>> All right. Hey, welcome to Pa.
>> I said to myself when I got to PA
tonight, uh, [laughter]
what? Oh, shout out to all you who
couldn't afford to go to Burning Man,
but you're still pulling down 3,500 a
month for rent. you know, I mean, takes
it takes takes some work to do that, but
uh no, I mean I we're not there because
we don't want to be. You got to want to
be for like years before you go, right?
And people know that who've been there.
And already I'm off subject, but um you
know, I got I got too much work. That's
that's why I'm not there. So, I work all
the time. In my more recent job, I I uh
got I've had a job uh cleaning mirrors
and um you know, it's something I can
really see myself doing. Um yeah. Yeah.
No, thank you. Uh that was, you know,
just a little warm up. You this heckle
night. I'm trying to tell my worst joke
so you guys be like, "Get the [ __ ] out
of here with that shit." You guys, um
you all cited Trump, Donald Trump, he he
renamed Lake Ontario. Yeah. How about
that? You guys excited about that? Lake
Lake Lake Gyllenhaal is what he's
calling it now.
Assalam alaikum. Assalam alaikum. Not
[laughter]
sorry. Oh man. How we doing? [ __ ]
well. Medium.
Rare. I'm doing a little rare myself. Uh
yeah. I don't know. Uh I'm all right
this week, but last week I was in rough
shape. I got a fight with that
cycllosporata.
Yeah, I took a overnight laxative. You
ever taken an over laxative?
Unbelievable product. You know, I took
one at midnight
and it aka Taco Bell. Uh, and I had the
most amazing movement at 700 a.m. The
tragedy was that I didn't wake up until
>> and I am not allowed back in that
Airbnb.
>> THAT WAS A [ __ ] JOKE. AH, THAT'S WHAT
I'M talking about.
High spice for this man. [laughter]
Thank you. That was a good one. Well
timed. All right. Oh, man. I uh been
trying to pass a drug test.
>> I know. I bought I bought seven bottles
of fake piss.
That's right. I drank seven bottles of
fake piss.
>> I know. And it didn't pass. [laughter]
I'm on the real piss now, though. I
know, right?
>> It's been rough. I'm telling you, it's
been rough. No, my dog my dog I think my
dog gave me fleas
and I didn't know that was a sexually
transmitted disease.
Where my Where are my dog [ __ ] at?
Dog [ __ ] Dog [ __ ] All right, one
more. One more.
One more. No, shout out to Jose. Thanks
for coming down, Jose. It's cool, man.
Giving us your time. It's a honor to uh
see your comedy over the years. And um
I've been saying mucho to my Hispanic
friends a lot. It means a lot, you know.
Uh [laughter] sorry. All right. I was
waiting for that one. Uh but uh
[laughter] that's a good one. All right.
Thank you. Thank you. I I should
probably end on that, but actually I
don't [laughter] know. Yeah. Getting
back to the cycllosporata, you know, I
had that other aka explosive diarrhea
and I called in my doctor and he put me
on hold.
>> Yeah. All right. All right. I'm getting
out of here. You guys have been real.
Appreciate you. Stick around. We got
funny [ __ ] coming up.
[applause]
>> Thank you. Keep it going for Morgan,
ladies and gentlemen. [applause]
Or is I never loot referred to him in
the chat section. Sean Penicellin.
That's hilarious.
>> That's hilarious. That should be your
new stage name. [ __ ] that's funny. Good
one. Talk to me later. Maybe you get
some hot sauce. All right, coming to the
stage right now. Possibly one of our
more uh polarizing comics. I think they
should have no problem heckling.
[laughter]
He tries to get you to heckle him on his
normal set. So, let's see if it works
this time. Ladies and gentlemen, give it
up for Bashure.
Okay.
>> I
>> Is it Is that What's going on? You guys
hear me? Okay.
>> You broke it.
>> [ __ ] [laughter]
>> This is my shot over here. And you guys
[applause]
are these obstacles in life,
>> right? That's that's what we look
forward in life. Um I My name is Bashar.
Okay. I am a cis brown
>> Muslim
male. Okay. I think I think it's right
up there in the most hated category with
like white sis males.
>> Okay. But the thing is they they deserve
it. Okay.
>> What did we What did we do? A building
or two. You guys bomb the [ __ ] out of
us. Okay. We You got yours back.
Okay.
[laughter]
I am I'm also going to a therapist.
You'd be happy to hear. Okay. Is this
true? And and my therapist is asking me
to connect with my inner child.
>> Okay. Like you sure?
>> She's like yes.
So I'm back bullying people now.
>> No.
>> Okay. And I got to admit it still feels
great.
Um once these guys done with their
conversation, are you the hecklers in
this conversation? Okay. Um
>> yeah, living on my for a while now. I I
um recently started my own business. You
guys give it up.
>> Thank you. Thank you. It's a
It's the American dream. I'm living it.
you know, and I'm setting up setting up
my Google account and Google was
suggesting I should mention I'm from a
minority, right? I was like,
I don't know if Muslim owned
is the missing piece of the puzzle to
this business. Okay. So, I just put uh
Muslim owned, LGBTQ operated,
and I'm renting a lot of scooters now.
Yeah, it works. It works.
>> Um, let's see. I think I think the table
has turned turned enough in the United
States where we can have a Muslim
superhero.
>> Would you guys would you guys be on
board with this one?
>> Hell yeah. Allah Akbar. That'll be
that'll be the catchphrase. Allah Akbar.
Everybody's running.
Okay. But I'm I'm not sure if I should
choose like a male or a female Muslim,
right?
>> Half and half. I was thinking a female
already comes in with a mask.
>> So that's a that's a plus. Okay. All
right. You guys are too good. Too nice.
The only thing I think she'll be she'll
know how to fly, but she can't drive.
She's she's from she's from Saudi
Arabia. That's that's our greatest ally.
Okay.
Okay, while we at it, I think we should
also have a Israeli
>> superhero, right?
>> And they'll just be like walking a
grandma across the street just doing
like the most mundane regular [ __ ] just
so we believe they actually human beings
at this point.
Okay.
>> Okay. Okay. Or like a Jewish superhero.
I think the only thing he'll save is
money.
Oh jeez.
>> Okay, nobody's standing for the Jews.
You guys can heckle you now. This is
your time.
Come on.
>> Okay. Uh this is It's all out of love.
What are you saying? Be careful. That's
crazy, right? [laughter]
>> That's crazy. That's why I flee Iraq,
right? But it's
>> okay. Well, you guys have been very
tolerant. Thank you very much. My name
is Bashar. Keep it going for the host.
[applause]
>> Keep it going for Bashar, ladies and
gentlemen. Not doing easy work there.
That's tough comedy. That's tough
comedy. You got in your faces. I [ __ ]
love it. Oh man. And hold on. Before we
continue, can we give it up for Skyler
switching a speaker in less than five
minutes? Did you see that [ __ ] DID YOU
SEE THAT [ __ ] That's why I hire the
best, ladies and gentlemen. That's why
he's our video producer.
>> Turn it back off.
>> Turn it back off. We can hear it. Oh,
the pain. Uh, hey, check out Shroom Cat
Studios if you guys uh have any sound or
video needs. If you need some sound for
events, Shroom Cat Studios, ask for
Skyler. He's the bomb, [ __ ] All right,
keeping it moving right along. Ladies
and gentlemen, a Monday favorite. If you
come here weekly, you know this act. You
probably love him. You may have no
ladies and gentlemen, Mr. Shahan Nelson.
[cheering]
[applause]
Hello, my name is Shane Nelson. Skyler,
that's straight NASCAR, dude. Super
dope. Super NASCAR.
Bashar, when you mentioned that like
women can't drive, even like
superpowered women can't drive.
Edgy. Um, this lady right here pointed
at him and said that this guy can't
park.
like we can't drive. This guy can't even
parallel park. Dude, stand up and show
your face. No, no, you can stay down.
But just so you know, there is a man. He
has a big beard. He looks like a manly
man. He cannot park. [laughter]
That's heavy. Standing up.
>> Yeah, we got Teslas. They park
themselves. [laughter] That's dope.
That's dope.
>> Park.
>> What' you say?
>> No. No thanks, dude. Um, [laughter]
what are you talking about, Wills? All
right. I uh I'm originally from North
Dakota. I'm Lakota from Standing Rock.
I'm Native American. And you're looking
at me. You're thinking, "This guy is a
Native American. This is how Native
American I am. I get free healthc care
for life."
>> Oh, that's like the dopest thing you can
get, dude.
>> Some people get educations. Blame.
[laughter] Free healthcare for life,
dude. I've lived on Maui for 15 years
and you know that if you move to Maui,
if you if you're not born and raised,
you never truly are a local, right? Like
I wanted to get like a Tacoma and a gold
chain so people would think I was local.
I can't afford that [ __ ] dude. But you
know what I can afford [laughter] is a
free dog from the Maui Humane Society,
dude.
>> And what's the most local dog? I GOT A
PITBULL.
>> AND WHAT'S THE MOST LOCAL KIND OF
PITBULL? I GOT TREELEGGED PITBULL, DUDE.
>> YEAH. His name is Bentley. He's super
dope, dude. I brought Bentley to Safeway
the other day and I left him in the car
with the windows down. I go in Safeway
and I'm shopping around. I'm looking at
eggs. That's how I say eggs. Eggs.
>> I'm from there.
>> Oh, you're from She says she's from
there. She's from the chicken coop, too.
Yeah. Bags. Eggs. Minnesota. North
Dakota. You know it's about
>> I'm looking for eggs. Enough. Let's let
her have her moment. She's a teacher.
She needs it. [laughter]
>> Right. She's not paid enough. She's not
paid enough.
>> We know that. So, I'm in Safeway. I'm
looking at eggs and this woman comes up
to me and she's like, "Do you have a
three-legged dog?" And I was like, "Yes,
I do." And she's like, "He's in aisle
7." I was like, "What's aisle 7?" She's
like, "Sausages." I WAS LIKE, "OH, NO.
[laughter]
WE HAVE TO GET HIM RIGHT AWAY, DUDE. He
looks like Scooby-Doo and he eats
sausages like Scooby-Doo." Like,
>> [laughter]
>> slurping them up. You know what I'm
saying?
>> Laugh at this [ __ ] [laughter]
>> Oh man. You You say I look like Shaggy
rolling
scoop. I can't do it by looking. And I
smoke a lot of weed and I sleep in a van
sometimes.
>> All right.
>> I was recently uh I was recently
recently having sex.
>> Good job. [cheering]
>> That's right. And I have sex sometimes.
And my girlfriend accused me of fart.
She smelled something stinky and she
accused me of farting. I did not fart.
Honest. Like, hand to God, I did not
fart. My dog, he farts during sex.
>> Yeah.
[laughter]
>> Dog farts are the worst. My dog farts
when he's
during sex. All right. [laughter]
I'm trying to I don't know how to say
it,
>> you know? Like I grew up in like the two
worst places to learn the English
language between Hawaii and North
Dakota. I I'm like a third grade level
when it comes to English, dude. I'm
making up words. I [laughter] use like I
use nar and moth a crazy amount.
>> I don't have enough No one knows what it
is, dude. I uh I don't have enough time
to get too into it, but I dated a
billionaire for a while. I I dated the
owner of the Oklahoma City Thunder.
Yeah. And I'm at a table full of
billionaires. How old is he?
>> How old was he?
>> He Oh, funny, dude. Cuz being gay is a
joke to you, Jimbo.
It's not a joke. They're people.
[laughter]
Gay. Gay people. How do you think you
were born, dude? Probably anal somehow.
You look like an anal baby. They're
rare, but they exist. Google it. Some
babies are born out of butts. And when
you see JIMBO TONIGHT, YOU'LL THINK THAT
IS A BUTT, BABY. [cheering]
>> MY NAME IS Shane Nelson. Goodbye.
[applause]
>> Mixing mixing farts and girlfriend
jokes. Give it up for Shahane Nelson,
ladies and gentlemen.
>> If you know ball,
how long have you been with her?
All right. No internet people here.
That's how you know. Chat's going to go
crazy. All right. coming to the stage
right now. Yes, you're next.
>> Yeah, he's next. Yeah, I just want to
double check. Coming to the stage right
now. No, he is not the smaller version
of your last comic. He is not the shot
that comes with your beer. He is another
person with feelings and you will treat
them as such. Ladies and gentlemen, give
it for Mr. Jackson Bayine.
[applause]
took a long
>> sets up an obstacle course and complains
how I do it.
>> All right. So, how early is too early to
start listening to Christmas music for
you people?
>> I want some answers here.
>> December 23rd.
>> December 23rd. That's still too early.
How else
>> dude? We I was on I was listening to the
radio on the way here
>> and they were playing Christmas music.
>> They were not.
>> They were
>> I shut it off. I I stopped listening to
music.
>> It's [ __ ] I used to work at a grocery
store.
>> Not a fun job.
>> That is the worst month to work at a
grocery store.
>> I was in New Hampshire bagging
groceries.
Not only was I freezing cold next to the
door, I had to listen to the bells and
[ __ ]
>> I uh I
>> I actually I got fired from that grocery
store.
>> Yeah, I bet you guys are surprised, huh?
>> Sorry.
>> No, I I didn't know that you could steal
something without leaving the store.
>> It was news to me.
I got off my break and as I was putting
my jacket back on,
>> I could smell myself. I was a little
ripe.
>> So, I went over to the deodorant
section, I grabbed a stick,
>> threw it on, and I put it in my pocket.
>> Okay.
>> And apparently,
>> one of the extra like vendors told on
me. So, I I go up and they they have a
whole serious meeting. They're showing
me the tape and [ __ ]
But the f like I just got off my break
before that. If they just rewinded the
tape to the beginning of my break, they
would have saw me go and grab a meatball
sub, grab a soda, grab a tub of Ben and
Jerry's ice cream, go in the back, eat
all of it, throw it away, pay for
nothing. They didn't actually even catch
me stealing
and I didn't want to work anymore that
day, so I went home anyway.
>> I'm confused on some of these
definitions.
>> What are your confused on my
definitions? My mom is also a teacher.
Let's see if we can figure this out. She
was an English major. Let's go. Come on.
>> So, you took a bunch of things. Yeah.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And you didn't pay for them.
>> No, but they didn't know about that
part. I just asked you didn't pay for
it.
>> No, no, no. That part was stealing.
>> Yeah.
>> I didn't pay for it.
>> Just wanted to get clear on that.
>> No. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Okay. And they said you stole.
>> Well, they didn't see that. They saw me
put it in.
>> You stole?
>> They did. Yes.
>> Right. And you just said you were
stealing.
>> Oh, yeah. 100%.
>> OKAY. THAT'S ALL.
>> [laughter]
>> SO LIKE that
that's that's kind of why I was you know
you know that's why I said it in the
order I said it in and stuff
>> excuse
>> if I wanted to that I would have just
told you I stole everything at the
beginning and then
>> you would have been accountable
>> actually here I have I have a I have a
reading joke for you
>> I want to hear it
>> okay
>> I read too I don't look like that
either. No, no. [laughter]
>> I uh I finished an autobiography not
that long ago, right? And I I got to the
end of the book and in like the final
pages, they had an about the author
page.
I know that table is not going to get
this joke, right? [laughter]
They're looking at me so [ __ ] blank.
>> Like about what?
>> All right, GOOD. I'M PROUD OF YOU. Do
you have a gold star we could [laughter]
give him? I don't. Um,
>> WHAT? YOU DON'T HAVE A GOLD STAR?
>> SORRY, I failed.
>> Nah, it's okay. I'll bring you a gold
star next week. It's fine.
>> Um, all right. So, this is more This is
more I'll do a I did a reading joke for
her. I'll do a joke for you guys at the
table. Are you Are you guys single here?
>> He didn't get it.
>> I didn't get it either.
It's every every page in the book is
about the author. It's an autobiography.
>> And then he put it at the end of the
book. Like that's like coming out with a
movie and then putting the trailer at
the end of your movie. You're just doing
it backwards.
>> I did it. You did. All right. He got it
before you did.
>> That's insane. All right. I ran out of
time here, guys. I'm Jackson Bay. Have a
good night.
[applause]
>> Keep it going for Jackson Bayine. Ladies
and gentlemen,
>> by the way, I heard what you said as a
defense. You're like, I'm trans and gay.
>> Which just means you're back to being a
cisgender male again. Like, do you
understand how that works? That's the
horseshoe. You just went all the way
back around. You're just
>> you're just a dude, get a [ __ ] hourly
job now. You're no longer special
anymore. You see how that works? back
around. I love that, dude. Um, Jackson
definitely looks like he worked at a at
a at a grocery store, right?
>> I could see that [ __ ] bag in my
my groceries. [laughter]
Like, what spe What special needs person
did he take that job from? I want to
>> Oh, he got fired. Those guys are in it
for life. I don't know if you seen
40-year-old specials back in your
grocery store still. He got cut, bro. He
got cut from that team. He got cut from
that team. What's your 40 speed, bro? We
got to figure that out. All right,
ladies and gentlemen, coming up next to
the stage, a man of many hairstyles, as
you'll see coming up soon, Mr. Joel
Huins,
[applause]
>> that's great. Everybody, keep it going
for Chino. HUH? [applause]
>> Our Messiah. That guy's great. Um, you
know, nobody's perfect, right? We all
have our flaws. Me, like, if I'm walking
around town, I'm a nice guy. But if I'm
driving, I'm a [ __ ] psychopath.
>> You know what I mean? Like somebody
could cut me off in traffic and I'll
yell something obscure. I'll be like,
"TAKE SOME INITIATIVE. GET YOUR [ __ ]
[ __ ] TOGETHER, DUDE." And then I'll go
back to listening to Tony Robbins on
Full Blast. [laughter]
There's some sad people in the crowd who
caught that one.
Yeah. Nobody's perfect, man. Nobody's
perfect. Uh, there's always something
that you want to change about yourself
or somebody else. Like me, I wish I was
black.
Truly, I mean, on paper, I'm halfway
there. I can dance. I can sing. I'm from
Atlanta. But hey, man, nobody's perfect.
Nobody's perfect. Nobody's perfect. Uh,
I wish I could change things about my
parents. When I call my parents, I wish
they'd stop ignoring my calls.
And they wish that I just wasn't a
comedian. You know,
that one hit a little too close to home.
That was like a very somber tone through
the room. That was a joke. That was a
joke. My parents are dead. Um,
[applause] they're not, but they hate
that joke. They hate that joke so much.
Um, let's see here. Uh, we all wish
there was something we could change
about ourselves or maybe our partners,
right? Like I wish that my girlfriend
didn't talk about our relationship
problems to chat GPT
and she wishes that I didn't cry and get
nosebleleeds during sex. But hey,
nobody's perfect, you know. Nobody's
perfect. Uh, nothing is perfect. Um, air
travel, air travel is definitely not
perfect. I got news for you. Something I
found out recently. If you're flying and
your gate agent says the flight is
delayed and she's also a black lady who
looks like she could bounce a club in
Detroit, that flight is not taking off.
All right, mental note, everybody, does
anybody uh everybody in here know what a
flash does anybody know what a flash
choir is? You know those guys that sing
out of nowhere?
I was on a redeye flight from LA to
Maui.
>> And at 1:00 in the morning, a bunch of
singers in unison, right? When they turn
the lights off in the plane, they go,
"I'm like a bird. I only fly away."
That's the reason you should be allowed
to take a handgun on an airplane.
I'd rather deal with a thousand crying
babies before I deal with one of those
ever again.
>> Yeah. Um, I recently got kicked off of
an airplane.
>> Holy what?
>> Yeah, I got I'm sorry, ma'am. Is there a
I'm sorry. Is there something more
amusing happening on your phone, ma'am,
in the front row?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, that's great. Thank you for that.
[laughter]
>> So amazing. Oh, thank you.
>> Hey, your shirt your shirt looks like
the carpet of a bowling alley in the
90s.
>> I mean, that's a compliment. I really
do. [laughter]
>> Yeah. No, I got kicked off of an
airplane in New York. Um, I deserved it.
I lost my [ __ ] for exactly half a second
and I punched the overhead compartment
three times as hard as I possibly could.
Um, so they kicked me off the plane and
I wasn't too happy about it. So I told
the male flight attendant that his pants
were too short for him and that he was
very ugly and that I bet his parents
were very proud of his flight attendant
daughter.
>> But hey,
nobody's perfect.
>> All right, guys. My name's Joel Huans.
That's my time. [applause]
>> Angry at an airport. Joel Huins. Ladies
and gentlemen,
>> I've been there. [applause]
I almost caught a case from TSA. I'm not
going to lie. I went through that stupid
little sensor machine where you got to
[ __ ]
>> And when it came around, I stepped out.
And you know how they got the little
screen that they can see and you don't?
>> I turned and looked circle dead square
in my crotch, big circle, and it says
abnormal bulge.
And me and the guy make eye contact. And
I just say, "Oh, it's abnormal."
And then he points to a sign that says,
"Any type of harassment of the TSC
agents will cost you $25,000 and 5
months in prison." And I was like,
>> "Was that harassment?" But that that was
that was kind of a joke. He's like,
"It's really up to me." And I was like,
>> "But you did smile a little bit, right?"
And he just went
>> I was like, "Oh, thank God. I almost
caught a case. But don't don't talk
about your dick to TS agents. Whatever
you do, [cheering]
>> don't say it's the bomb. Don't say
you're packing. Don't say any of that
[ __ ] It's not worth it. You'll be stuck
in LaGuardia. I guarantee it." All
right. And when they put their hands in
your back, don't say I need a cigarette.
>> Not a good thing.
>> They don't give you a cigarette.
>> Don't say, "I need a cigarette."
>> Right. I thought a cigarette and a soda
is what they give you, right? That's not
No, I thought that's the one thing. And
a phone call. Those are Oh, no. Those
are the cops afterwards. That's who that
is. Sorry about that. I watched too much
CSI. That's my fault. All right. Uh, Mr.
You're up next, right?
>> Yeah. You ready?
>> He's ready. Yeah, he's ready. Ladies and
gentlemen, coming up next to the stage,
the only person I have to raise the mic
stand for, get Mr. E.
[applause]
>> Thank you. Thank you. Keep going for
Gino. Everybody,
[applause]
>> I in honor of Peckle night, I thought
I'd make it easy. There's got to be some
people want to pick on hippies or
something.
>> I'm kind of used to getting picked on. I
thought this might be fun. being being
the brightheaded stepchild. I got a head
start on you all. Please,
>> somebody swing at me.
>> No one.
>> I'm the bastard son of a minister, so
they don't even want to talk about me. I
guess I'm not surprised,
>> man. Man,
the one time nobody wants to pick on me.
What? Why? This isn't fair.
>> There's so many reasons to pick on me.
No one.
>> I didn't hear it.
>> I mean, I I don't even know where to
begin to pick on me.
>> I am the taco eating contest. Two time
winner.
>> I I've eaten so many psychedelics that
like like enough for a party is probably
a micro dose for me. I don't I don't
even get high on LSD anymore. I just
verify that it's not something else.
It's not fair.
I miss the good old days when things
still worked. You didn't have to have
three extra tests to make sure they were
okay for your friends. What happened to
the world
for a while? They started a nested my
brother too. I mean, if you don't have
somebody that died, you're not on Earth.
I mean, let's be honest. You guys, as
long as you lock into the the duality
complex, you're you're you're stepping
into mortality and it, you know, free
will. Wizards first rules. People get to
believe whatever they want. Regardless
of how ignorant, selfish, or stupid it
is, they still get to believe it.
>> I think this comedy show is living proof
cuz they let me on stage.
>> Somebody's got to pick on me. The job is
heckle night. What drugs are you on?
>> There you go.
>> Right now, I'm high on life.
>> I was about to be on nicotine, but my
job came up. I've actually been really,
really boring. I had my birthday at the
beginning of the month, and all I've
done since then is smoke weed pretty
much.
>> Maybe a couple squares of mushroom
chocolates.
>> Actually, I had an orange sunshine that
was legitimately made by Timothy Liry,
like those old turmeric crusties. That
was [ __ ] awesome. That was That's
such a happy acid.
It's weird, you know, like the original
Albert Hoffman recipe, it's a
synthesized
ergonine, so you has to run through all
these different columns and substrates
and filters and it has to get diluted
into the specific environment with
non-acquous solution. So like the
original LSD is really filtered and
structured. So it's like this refined
essence of a power, the light of
creation. But the orange sunshine that
stuff from Weiri and and all them it it
it's ALD52 because there was a time when
ALD 52 wasn't a scheduled drug but ALD52
would hit your stomach and then become
LSD25. So that one wasn't like that
structured refine. It was more like that
happy birth. Like if any of you are into
the troll, like the sunshine feels like
the ace of a cup of a suit and the
sunshine feel or like the the original
family white feels like a 10 of that
suit if that makes sense to intellectual
minds. [laughter]
>> I'm glad it makes sense to someone. I
might have a couple new clients after
this set. [laughter]
At least I know the difference between
Swiss and needle point and family white
and check and what they're for.
One minute I start talking about acid in
4 minutes disappear. What happened?
>> Surprised
for my cred. I did earn this grateful
dead bear holding a 13pointer at the
Oregon Country Fair. I got that tattooed
for to reader read behind the further
bus.
>> [applause]
>> So you work it.
>> How did you earn it?
>> Oh, so after my time in Iraq, I realized
how shitty being in Iraq was and I
didn't like how filthy my soul felt. So
I did atonement and I I sat in aesthetic
poverty at the gateways of the rainbow
revolution primarily like Hayden
Ashberry Eugene. [laughter] I protected
young ladies. I gave out so many
crystals and fun stuff. I service you
asked. Oh no. You let my story carry it
a little bit further. This is all her
fault. Everyone, let's heckle her.
>> Everybody help me heckle HER A SECOND.
>> NO.
>> IF YOU'RE GOING to heckle, you got to be
funny.
>> You're done.
>> All right. On that note, I'm a big
enough. I'm going to let somebody else
get picked on. Have a great night,
everyone. Give it back to you. Once
again, I'm Mr. E.
[applause]
>> Keep it going for Mr. Three, ladies and
gentlemen. [applause]
[snorts]
>> Yeah, you know what? Pass. I'm not even
[laughter] going to I have like three
different angles, but you know what? I'm
just
[applause] I'm just going to keep
swiping. But you know what I am going to
do? I'm going to let you know that we're
going to give a big thank you to our
sponsor, High Spice. Highspice Hot Sauce
sponsors this. Check out their website
if you want to get some hot sauce. If
you can't see us in person,
highspice.com. hispice.com.
Type in coms sim 10. Get 10% off your
order anywhere in America. Check it out.
Highspice. Someone here is going to get
a free bottle of Highpice tonight. I
guarantee it. I promise it. All right.
Coming to the stage next, the moderator
of our chat room, which means that he's
the man that dons the biohazard gear and
scrubs through the [ __ ] for the gold.
>> One of my good friends and one of yours
now, too. Get up for Mr. Jimbo slice.
Keep it going, Vino.
[applause]
Much better. Now, I I am that guy from
earlier. Shane's right. I am a butt
baby. And I look like a butt baby, BUT
IT'S NOT THAT TYPE OF BUTT BABY. I'M
JUST REALLY [ __ ] POOR.
It's like, JIMBO, BE A BUTT BABY OR EAT
BALONEY.
What would you choose? I do both.
[laughter] It's terrible.
Um, man, YOU KNOW, SHANE'S LIVED OUT
here 15 years. Uh, you know, so he knows
a lot about this island. He actually
helps me out. Um, with all these
hurricanes coming, I watch Shane and how
he hurricane preps. It's It's [ __ ]
genius. He does it every rule. Who
thinks that they hurricane prep better
than Shane?
>> That's what I thought. I know you don't.
[laughter]
Hurricane. Uh, Shane actually preps for
hurricanes by downloading all of his
porn.
He's smart.
>> All right, I'm just kidding. Shane
doesn't watch porn. [laughter] Shane's
actually a porn star. You can look him
up.
>> Nash the Stash. Sorry. Sorry. I told him
I never would. Um, anybody out there
watch porn?
>> I know you do. [laughter] YOU DID NOT
NEED TO TELL US THAT. We see that
haircut. We know. We know. We know your
categories already. [laughter]
Oh man. Uh, tiny tortoise. [laughter]
That's weird. He created categories.
I think porn needs to be studied. Just
not like how he studies it, but porn
needs to be studied because porn has
like totally missed the epidemic of ads
and advertising. Like I know there are
ads in porn, but it's just other porn.
>> True.
>> Says the guy the only guy that watches
porn in here. That's true. And if you
all knew that, you would have laughed at
that. You're like watching porn and you
look in the corner and you're like, "Oh,
other anal."
>> How how should they do it?
>> Clean up. Why? You, sir, do not strike
me as someone who cleans up. [laughter]
Can we pan the camera over there? So I
look funny to the online viewers.
Thank you. [laughter]
>> I could I bet you smell good but just
stick. It's everything. [laughter]
>> It's terrible. I know. ANYONE ELSE OUT
THERE THINK THEIR algorithm is just not
true?
Yeah. It's like I'm sick of people that
are acting like it's not 100% perfect.
Like I'm scrolling and it's like
gambling,
gambling addiction, [laughter]
gambling class action lawsuits.
WHAT IS THIS [ __ ] SO I HIT THE three
dots like Instagram, relax. I don't want
to see this. I see it too much. It's
irrelevant. I got an email back from
Instagram and said, "We received your
request. Bullshit." [laughter]
It's like we literally watch your
[ __ ] screen. We know. We know what
you look at. Midgets, [laughter]
tiny tortoise.
My algorithm's [ __ ] It's like
nitrous. Nitrous lawsuits.
[ __ ] [laughter]
I'm gambling. Which lawsuit is going to
make me more money?
It's tough. It's hard. It's tough [ __ ]
I think I [ __ ] up my algorithm. Just
one night on nitrous gambling.
Gone down the drain. Forgive me. I'm
human. mystery.
Oh man, I um I have a dog. Any dog
lovers out there? Hell yeah. I love
dogs. Um I have a dog. He's old. He's 13
years old. He is a pitbull Rhodesian
Ridgeback. Don't clap cuz he's old.
Clap. CLAP CUZ IT'S ALMOST OVER.
[laughter]
OH, shut up. I raised him. He's a good
[ __ ] dog, too. Uh but he's on a lot
of pain pills cuz he tore all four of
his CCLs chasing after [ __ ]
Like father like son. He tore all four
of his CCLs. He's on a bunch of pain
pills and the the vet really cares about
him. Cuz in the mail the other day, I
got a letter that said, "If you take
your dog off these pain pills, don't do
it all at once, you know, do it
gradually because if you do it all at
once, that dog could end up suffering
from severe depression or even become
suicidal."
I SAID, "NOT MY CHESTER, MY CUTE little
waggy boy Chester. No way he could be
depressed or suicidal. [ __ ] that [ __ ] I
took him off the pain pills. Remember,
I'm poor. Took him off the pain pills
and I'll be damned. I came home from
work the other day and there he was in
the corner of the living room sports
betting and doing whippets
>> like father like son. ALL RIGHT
EVERYBODY, MY NAME IS JIMBO. LET'S KEEP
IT GOING FOR your host Chino. I love you
with my whole heart chat. All of you
incelss.
Jimbo coming out swinging. He wants that
set. I can tell. One more time for Jimbo
slice. Ladies and gentlemen,
[applause]
you know, a lot of you guys don't
notice, but that's what it looks like
when a big guy gives his effort. That's
what it looks like. That's what it looks
like. Little spit, little sweat. That's
what I like to see. Good [ __ ] Jimbo.
Good [ __ ]
>> All right, ladies and gentlemen, coming
up next to the stage, the poet, the man,
and now the comic. Give it up for
Joshua.
[applause]
>> Any uh
critiques for my uh comedy so far.
>> Looks like I got one.
>> It's uneven.
[clears throat]
>> And you can't see it. IT'S GOING TO
BOTHER YOU.
>> YEAH.
What What exactly is your problem?
KEEP [laughter]
GOING. Keep going.
>> I'm I'm curious. It's a serious
question.
>> Your voice is hilarious.
>> My voice makes you nervous.
>> No, hilarious.
>> Oh, hilarious. Okay. [laughter]
>> Any other critiques? [laughter]
>> Darn it.
Yeah, you have a pink dude.
>> You said it.
>> Why is it a problem?
>> It's not.
>> Okay. You have some poetry?
>> YES.
>> Air time. Air time, [applause] bro. Air
time. But you're a poet. [clears throat]
>> No.
>> Okay.
[laughter]
>> Word.
Deep.
>> So deep. So deep. You can't even hear
it.
>> I AM GOOD.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> YEAH.
>> GIVE THE TIME BACK TO the room. Can we
go for Joshua?
>> Yo, this girl just started laughing
before he even talked and that was like
the showstopper for the set. That was
that's that stopped everything. All
momentum. She just went to
>> She hit him with the [ __ ] release the
balloon sound.
>> She didn't even full belly.
[laughter]
>> Like TV static. That [ __ ] was brutal.
All right. Hey, good try, Joshua. That's
fine. That's very fine. That's mighty
fine.
>> And your beard is not uneven. It's not
uneven. All right. [laughter]
I mean, I'm not going to bust out a
level. Maybe to some degree it's
asymmetric, but that's beauty. That's
not beards. That's just All right,
>> ladies and gentlemen.
>> Come up next to the stage. Uh, a
comedian who is many people at different
times. I don't know who he's going to be
tonight, but he told me to introduce him
as just one name, one word, four
letters. Keep it going for Earl.
[applause]
Go back to where
the [ __ ] you doing, [ __ ] Earl.
>> [ __ ] YOU.
>> YEAH, [ __ ] YOU, TOO.
>> [ __ ] Earl. I'll be honest with you.
I'm bummed the [ __ ] out tonight.
AND IT'S ROUGH DAY WITH THE OLD DIVORCE
and [ __ ] Be yourself.
>> That's not a [ __ ] joke.
>> BE YOURSELF BY YOURSELF. STAY AWAY FROM
ME.
>> All right.
>> THAT'S [ __ ] PAN per
[ __ ] ANYWAYS, I'VE BEEN HITTING THE
SAUCE A little early.
>> You don't say,
>> you know,
>> ANY DEGENERATE DRUNKS HERE IN THE
AUDIENCE?
We ought to hang out
AND MY FRIEND HE G ME ONE of them
[ __ ] weed crispy marijuana infused
[ __ ] candy bar type deals tells me to
eat a fifth of it.
>> I ATE THE WHOLE [ __ ] THING AND DRANK
A FIFTH of tequila. That's right.
>> SO I'M IN A [ __ ] UP POSITION WHERE I
THINK ANYTHING I say right now is
[ __ ] hilarious.
But I also am pretty sure that a sizable
segment of this [ __ ] audience is a
goddamn fed.
And you're here to get ME OVER SOME
CRIME. I can't even remember
[ __ ] committing.
AND I'M HIGH ENOUGH THAT I PROBABLY
FORGOT THE CRIME. And I'm drunk enough
that I definitely committed it.
SO NEEDLESS TO SAY, ALL THAT [ __ ] I
WROTE DOWN as a joke to tell before ye
and God and the AUDIENCE AND everyone
that Oh [ __ ] Um, how far is THAT STEP?
ANYWAY, I FORGOT THAT [ __ ] I CAN'T even
remember my [ __ ] name.
But what I do know is some of y'all's
talking [ __ ]
>> HALF ASS.
HALF ASS.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, I GOT FULL ASS, but if I show it,
I'm not going to be allowed around
schools and [ __ ]
>> Okay.
>> You weren't already.
>> All my feet.
>> SHOW YOUR FEET.
>> SHOW WHAT THE [ __ ] DO you think this is?
>> ALL RIGHT. FIRST OF ALL, I didn't know
chicks had foot fetishes. I know a lot
of dudes do cuz [ __ ] with foot
fetishes don't they tell you like I got
a person I work with with a foot fetish.
I should not know this.
But the [ __ ] got to like put
their foot in the water and be like,
"Are you you too? You too? You into
this?"
>> And the [ __ ] up part is he's
complimented my shoes and my slippers a
whole bunch. At first I was like, "Well,
that's normal. Thank you." And now I'm
looking back on it. I'm like, "Ew,
[ __ ] look at my feet."
Now I can't go down that road. That get
me fired from my [ __ ] job. Anyways,
um
>> uh [ __ ]
>> wizards. I You know what? I'mma talk
about wizards.
>> I looked at Mr. E. I thought wizards.
So, I heard this story the other day
that blew my [ __ ] mind. So, anybody
know who Alistister Crowley is?
>> So, Alistister Crowley was this [ __ ]
magician and he was like a dark
magician. Not not as in skin tone or
anything like that, but as in Anyways, I
got a minute left, so I'm going to tell
this story. So,
Alistister Crowley did this ritual where
he summoned a demon into another man's
body. And he did all this work to summon
this demon. And you know what he did?
>> What?
>> He [ __ ] the the dude that he
summoned the demon into.
AND YOU KNOW HOW LIKE IMAGINE you're
just a demon in hell doing your own
thing and then all of a sudden
I WILL NOT SHOW MY FEET. FEET are
disgusting. [ __ ] it. I got the opposite
of that. But imagine you're in hell and
you're just mining your and THEN YOU'RE
JUST BROUGHT UP INTO SOME DUDE'S BODY
AND THEN [ __ ] BY ALISTISTER
CROWLEY.
>> THE AUDACITY OF THAT MAN. OH,
>> ANYWAYS, that's my time. [ __ ] y'all.
[applause]
[cheering]
>> Keep going. Keep going for Earl, ladies
and gentlemen.
>> Earl.
>> And the deeper thing you're not
examining, Earl, is that he is a demon.
So, he's never had an [ __ ] because
he's never lived. So, he's thrust into
this body and all of a sudden he has his
first [ __ ] and it's immediately
[ __ ] by Alistister Carly. Like, we
need to focus on that.
>> [laughter]
>> He doesn't even know the joys of
[ __ ] yet. He hasn't even used it
properly yet. He's just like, "Where am
I? There's daylight. Why is there
something in my ass?" That poor demon.
Yeah, that's a good point. Sorry, I just
wanted to elaborate. You were making
good points.
>> That's how you end a bipolar episode,
ladies and gentlemen.
[applause]
>> When someone's like, "You think we
landed on the moon?" I'm like, "You
still believe in space, [ __ ]
You got to go further." All right,
ladies and gentlemen, coming up to the
stage, one of our most physical
performers to date. Give it up for Mr.
Ivan Nathansson.
[cheering]
[applause]
>> Let's go where?
>> To the men's.
>> To the men's room.
>> That's where you're taking me. That's
the first date.
>> That's the first date. All right, good.
Awesome. Not even a drink, nothing. It's
just Let's go to the men's room. All
right.
>> What
>> if you What?
>> Where you from?
>> Argentina.
>> Okay.
>> You know where it is? You're the
teacher, right?
>> No.
>> She's the teacher.
>> What? She You're You're low on your
cardio.
>> Which one are you?
>> All right.
Class, please.
>> Here.
Guys, give me five minutes, please. I
know you're eating. Just give me five
minutes. I'll meet you in the men's room
later, but give me five minutes.
>> All right.
If you see me glowing tonight, it's the
anti-depressants.
You guys, please give me five minutes or
share what you're saying, please. It's
very interesting.
Uh,
>> give him your number already. Come on.
>> All right.
>> Am I supposed to heckle you?
>> Yeah, sure.
>> Yeah. Yeah, sure. Yeah, whatever.
[laughter] How many drinks you had?
>> Me?
>> Yeah.
>> I have three.
>> All right. Get him the number, please.
Already. No. All right.
>> Comb your hair.
>> What?
>> Go to hell.
>> Comb your hair. Come. Oh, it never
comes. It Yeah. Do you want to see this?
>> You want to see this? You have You got
OCD, right?
>> NO,
>> ONE AT A TIME.
>> You're align.
>> Do you guys have this thing where you
see like the clock going like 111?
You're like, "Oh, this means something."
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's psychotic. We need to stop
that. [laughter]
It's terrible, dude. Yeah. The other day
I got into my car, I turn on the stereo
and it says receiver and I'm I already
know I'm bisexual, but now I'm gay.
[laughter] [ __ ]
That's how life is decided.
Men's room. Anything?
>> Let's go.
HOW many of us are going to the men's
room?
>> Are
the men's room?
>> That's
>> You have to pay more for me. That for
sure. I'm way more expensive.
>> Two, it's three is a crowd,
>> you know. But after my
>> What do you say about my hair?
>> No. Hurry up. Radio
[laughter]
>> for now.
>> All right.
>> After my uh first uh
threesome with two guys,
they laugh at [ __ ] They probably go get
out of here and go like, "I'm straight.
I'm straight." But now you're like, "Ah,
he's gay." Okay. [laughter]
After my first threesome with two guys,
I realized I love uh birds. I I am a
bird watcher.
Every time I get a hard on now, I think
I can go for a cockatu.
>> Yeah, we're having a lot of fun in the
men's room day later.
>> [ __ ] yeah.
I love [ __ ] puns.
>> I'm a pansexual.
>> A pansexual.
>> No more drinks for table two. I don't
know. [laughter]
>> Okay, this one is This one is for you.
>> Do you know what's vegan and dyslexic's
favorite singer?
Helen color
>> that's another vegetable good but it's
not the one Elvis parsley
>> and I'm going to leave you with this one
uh I don't know if you know Ompics but
there's a cheaper version if you're into
that there's a cheaper version comes
from Mexico it's called hosmpics
[applause]
you get so thin so thin that eyes won't
find you.
And that's my time. Thank you so much.
My name is Ivan.
[cheering and applause]
>> Give it up for Ivan, ladies and
gentlemen. [cheering]
All right, guys. We got four comics left
on the list. There's still a little bit
of room, too. So, anybody else want to
try to do comedy? Get yourself on the
list. If not, we got four more left.
Trisha edition is going to be walking
around with a tip jar collecting tips.
If you got any money to throw it towards
us for the comedy simulator, we would
appreciate it. Throw it in the tip jar.
If you don't, we'll remember it forever
and we will hold it against you always.
I'm just joking. But I do have a Venmo,
too, so there's no excuses. All right,
>> ladies and gentlemen, four more left.
Are we ready for the home stretch?
>> Make some noise if you're ready for the
home stretch.
[cheering]
>> Your first of four final comics coming
to the stage. She was joined us last
week and now she's back. Get her for
Sasha.
[cheering]
>> [applause]
>> Thank you, Chino. You're Kiki. Yes.
Yeah. Who Who here is Kiki Okina?
>> Okay, I got one. The Yeah. So, yeah, I I
can tell by that that uh No, the answer
for most people is no. That that means
you're born here. I was born here,
believe it or not, but my teachers from
first to 12th grade were from the
mainland, which is why I sound like chat
GPT.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> So, I'm going to go down some
welltraveled territory as a comedian and
talk a little bit about dating. Who here
is on the apps? Anybody? you've all
found love and are happy and aren't
swiping left and slowly losing hope.
Congratulations.
I actually did take a break from the
apps um a little over a year ago. Uh cuz
you know, as much as I actually did
enjoy getting dickpicks from dudes as
soon as I gave them their number, I
mean, I'm not complaining. It wasn't
bad. Um, you know, I thought this is
probably not the path to a real
relationship. So, I decided, you know
what? I'm going to meet people in
person. I'm going to let people Yeah.
meeting people in person, being a human.
Yeah. Uh, you know, so I I thought,
yeah, let let me let somebody set me up.
So, you know, my cousin's wife uh
wanted to set me up and she is a doctor
and she had met a guy at a medical
conference and she's telling me about
him and she's like, "Yeah, he you know,
he seems really cool. He's from South
Africa." I was like, "Wait, hold up,
hold up. He's from South Africa." And I
was like, "Okay, so like like what kind
of South African, right?" I was like,
"Is he like Zulu?" and and and she's
like
>> you in space balls.
>> Oh, thank you. [laughter]
May the shorts be with you. Uh so,
you know, uh she she's I'm just like,
"Well, what is he white?" And she's
like, "Yeah, he's white." And I'm like,
"So, like, what kind of white?" And
she's like, "Well, I don't know what you
mean." And I was like, "You know, like
is he Dutch South African?" And she's
like, "I don't know. Like, like he's a
white dude." She She told me his name
and I was like, "Oh, okay. He is he is
in fact Dutch South African. Um and you
know my first thought when I heard that
was you know it starts with a ray ends
with a cyst. H you know our good friend
Elon Musk not not a great look. But then
I thought to myself you know you are the
one who's being a racist. How can you
assume that this man is a racist just
because of his background? What? Yeah.
Charlies Theren is Dutch South African.
Everyone says she's amazing. He could be
like the boy Charlies Theren. You don't
know. So it's like, keep a [ __ ] open
mind, right? How are you going to date
if you don't have an open mind? So I'm
like, you know what? Yeah, let let's do
it. And she's like, yeah, he loves
hiking and and you know, so do we. So we
could all go on a hike together. I'm
like, yeah, let like let's do it. And so
around this time, I'd started working in
her office, so we were co-workers. And I
get to work one day and everybody's
talking about this South African
anesthesiologist from Maui who pushed
his wife off a cliff. And I was like,
"OH, THAT'S really funny cuz you know a
a South African anesthesiologist
who likes hiking." And she's like, "It's
him." And I was like, "You're kidding.
You're kidding." She's like, "No, no,
like really, it's him." And
and it turns out, yeah, the last text
that he sent to her was, "I can't wait
to go hiking with you." So, yeah, I
know. So, like, I'm not sure. Like, so
so I mean, the good news is, okay, the
bad news is he's married. The the good
news is I mean, he was planning on being
single, I guess, or was he just like
practicing with her so that he could
also push us off a cliff? I don't know.
[laughter]
Um, I mean, so the moral of the story is
it actually would have turned out to be
much better. And I I would never
normally say this, but like it would
have been better if he were racist. He
he's he's in prison now. He's convicted
of attempted murder. It was in People
magazine. Uh, you know. So, in
conclusion, I I am back on the apps. I'm
still single, but yeah, but but I am
getting some world class dickpicks, and
that's all that matters. Thank you very
much.
[applause]
>> Yo, give it over Sasha
>> who said that she'd rather her date be
racist
>> than a than a attempted murderer.
>> Okay, can we be honest for a second?
That's an attempted murderer.
The only crime he committed was trying.
[laughter]
>> He in fact did not kill anybody.
>> I argue. Was there a crime committed
that day? No, there was. He stabbed her
with a needle. It was a terrible
happening. It was all over the papers.
[ __ ] that guy. I'm literally trying to
be funny. That is not okay.
But is it? No. All right, we got three
more left. We're gonna we're gonna
ramping this down. You guys ready for
the next one coming up?
>> You guys ready for the next one? Uh,
[applause]
>> she's not listed as a comic and I
believe there may be interpretive dance
going on with this. I don't know what's
going on with this. There's all types of
stuff going on. Next month coming up,
first time on our stage. Give it for me
the poet. Ladies and gentlemen,
[cheering]
[applause]
Hi.
>> Hi. I'm Mir the poet. Usually I do this
with payment Gino. So properly after
this, please give me my monies. Thank
you. Thank you very much. Hi. My real
name is Ramira and I'm from Big Island
as you can see. Big Island.
>> Oh. Oh, here you go. Here you Here we
go.
>> Big island. Got it. Good. Good. Good.
Good. Good. Good. BEAUTIFUL. BEAUTIFUL.
NOW, OH NO. UHUH. THAT'S IT. THAT'S ALL
YOU GET. THAT'S ALL YOU GET. It is what
it is. Get over it now.
So, I'm not a comedian at all
whatsoever. Actually, let me go ahead
and strip a little bit for you all. So,
I am Yeah, I know you like that. So, I'm
not a comedian really. I'm more of I'm
more of a poet, as Gino said. And I got
some very sensual
poetry for you all. All right. So, it's
a little something something that I did
long ago. And I got my birthday girl
Katrina to do interpretive dance. IT'S
HER BIRTHDAY, Y'ALL. GIVE IT UP FOR
THAT. GIVE IT UP for that. HER BIRTHDAY
GANG GANG. COME ON. Virgo season. I'm an
Aries. But it's okay. We'll have her We
have her season to shine. That's fine.
That's fine. That's all right. Okay.
>> It is what it is. But Aries is number
one always.
>> Yes. Yes.
>> All right. So, this poem
is called Candy [ __ ]
CC. All right.
All right. And so, Katrina got a poll
here to use for this beautiful poem that
I made long ago. Y'all ready?
>> Y'all ready?
>> ALL RIGHT. [laughter] OKAY. COME ON.
>> All right. Candy [ __ ]
The climax
after every stimulated release, after
the satisfaction by the season stroked
of his tongue.
After my vocals wailed with
emancipation,
[laughter]
>> I can't help. Yeah, like the
proclamation. Exactly. Exactly. I can't
help but ask,
>> "How did it taste?"
>> [laughter]
[applause]
>> Hell yeah.
>> I get a little chuckle, but I'm always
given the same answer.
It tastes like nothing.
>> Uh-uh.
A whole bunch of nothing, too. And I'm
slightly disappointed.
It isn't the flavor of sweet nectar or
peaches and cream with a honey pot pink
as pion. I expected a distinct zest of
the ripest strawberry preserves
to be a decadent chocolate doughut with
a rich jelly filling.
To my annoyance, my yoni isn't the
pentacle of savory delights.
And subconsciously, I want it to taste
better. Taste like something special.
You hear me? Special.
I ate pineapples. Nothing.
I've eaten less meat. Nothing.
Over and over. I feel tasteless, plain,
and nothing.
>> My higher self nonetheless enlightened
me day by day, teaching me in its own
way. I now see the gift I was given from
birth, formulated generations through my
maternal ancestors. I cleanse a men's
pallet
with flowering waters. I sample a
clarity of for taste buds of my vagina
is sugarcoated for fleet wants but
thirst quenching as a bare necessity.
Its hydration from a heavy foreplay, a
watering hole for only the welldeserved
specimen. My powerhouse untainted and
natural is an appetizer. A refresher
before the main course.
Now, where is my head now with this
knowhow? Living contently, fully, and in
the moment in every steamy moment.
That was Candy Clip.
[applause]
>> And that's all I got for y'all. Like I
said, I really get paid for this, but
you know, IT'S A LITTLE A LITTLE
birthday thing for my girl OVER HERE,
YOU KNOW. SO, it is what it is. IT'S ALL
YOU GET.
GREAT WORK, LADIES. Keep it going.
Premier Mirror the poet. [applause]
>> Yo, I don't know. I don't know. I don't
know if you you looked stage right at
all,
>> but she was like Katy Perry's left shark
in that was just
she was giving full effort the entire
time.
Jimbo, stop trolling.
>> Hey, you heard her. You want more? You
got to give the girl some money. You
better pay her. You better pay this
lady. All right, [cheering]
coming to the stage currently.
>> A comedian of the West Side has been
joining us.
>> Okay. What the hell is going on here?
All
>> [applause]
>> right, we good
as became Monday Night Raw. What's going
on over here, boys and girls?
>> All I know is either way, wrestling or
[ __ ] We're going to need a lot of oil
for that one. That's for sure.
>> There was an oil spill in Maui. Do tell.
Um, all right. [laughter]
We got a few more comics left. We're
bringing this bringing this night down.
Ladies and gentlemen, your next comic uh
from the west side has been joining us
for a while. Oh, Roy's goodness. They're
always happy to see him. Get him for
Craig.
[cheering]
[screaming]
>> Oh god. How do you [applause]
squeeze?
>> How does this thing work?
>> I want to raise them. Oh, squeeze it,
guys.
>> All right. Let's see.
>> All right.
I was working I work at the pool.
[laughter]
>> This I work at the pool. I'm a pool
lifeguard. And uh today I heard a pool
joke. A local pool joke from a guy named
Alica. He pro probably know. Anyway, he
said,
"What do you call a guy with no left
arm, no left leg?" All right. All right.
That's our That's a local joke to warm
you up.
>> So, as I mentioned last week, I'm a
student at the community college.
Turns out that the other kids in school
like me. I'm making new friends.
>> It's a good time.
>> Stay away from kids.
>> Oh, hey. Hey, dude. Hey, old guy with
the the hat. He's looking down. Anyway,
we Hey, hey, hey, you remember we uh we
broke down FuzzFest together for Trevor.
Remember that?
>> Oh, yeah. All right. Everybody knows
Trevor, too.
Uh,
>> so let's see what's going on, man. Um,
I'm taking a uh ceramics class. That's a
good time. Just touch clay for the first
time in my life. It was a really good
time. It's kind of It's kind of sexy in
a weird way. Uh, taking this cool acting
class
>> from this cool professor named Audi. You
know Audi? Everybody knows Audi.
Audi's cool. I had to do I had to do
homework this morning at 6:00. It was
due at 8. Had to go to work before after
that. I had to make a one a one minute
video selling myself.
>> And I it took me two years of being a
student at the community college to
realize I could do that all on my phone.
[laughter] I've been using laptops and
real computers thinking that's how I had
to do [ __ ] Kind of an old guy.
Oh. Anyway, uh so in Audi's class I had
to sell myself. So I said, you know, I
had to do a 60 minute 60second thing,
you know, setting myself apart.
So I said, you know, uh
I uh let's see what I say. I said, I'm
capable of anything afraid of nothing
except rock climbing.
And uh then at the end of it, I said,
and furthermore,
they're probably very few I might be the
only candidate that is a qualified
bonafide supercalifragilistic
xpalidocious candidate. Anyway, that was
what I did for homework this morning.
And then I went to work at the pool at
the county pool. It's the best freaking
job ever. Oh my god.
I love going to work. I love going to
work. I clean pools for a living. I
watch people swimming back and forth.
It's a good time. Let's see. Uh I'm
trying to do this, you know, like using
my brain and it's not easy.
All right, let's see what else going on.
Um,
>> it's so hard.
>> That one guy said he can he's a good
dancer with a beard and long I don't
think he's a good dancer, first of all.
>> I just want to say that. I'm sorry.
>> Oh, I'm getting some I'm getting
heckled. I'm getting heckled.
>> Oh. Yeah.
>> When I'm with my kids and we see a
homeless person talking to themselves, I
say to them, I turn to my kids. I say,
"Hey, that guy was once married."
>> What else? What else? I forget where I
was going with Where was I going with
all this anyway?
>> Um I don't know what I'm doing. It's my
first day every day. Hey, listen. If you
don't think I'm funny, my ex-wife agrees
with you.
She told me, Craig, you are not funny.
[laughter] Only thing that's funny is
you think you're funny.
>> Anyway,
what else is going on? Oh, the Sophie
swim, everybody. The Sophie swim. It's
coming up September 13th. Any of you are
swimmers, come on down. Swim that Sophie
swim.
>> Be cool. Go to the pool.
>> Train. Stop talking and dance.
>> Twerk. I want to see you twerk.
>> What else? God. Oh man.
>> You're not gonna make fun of somebody.
>> Oh, hey. Let's make fun of Noah. Have
you Have you seen Jonah Hill?
>> No. I don't care about
>> see you dance.
>> Oh, you're funny. So,
>> you can't make fun of somebody.
>> God, I had a fat joke about myself. I
can't remember it. Anyway,
Oh, you're so hard. You're so hard on
me.
>> No, you're talking about
>> I think I just about done and I really
This is my As you can see, that's my
first day every day. Um, good times
though. G Whiz, thanks for having me.
Um, I'll come back next week. Tell you
what's going on in school and at the
pool.
All right,
>> give it a go for Craig, ladies and
gentlemen.
>> Hey, I think that's the first night the
first time he's ever had two women
screaming twerk at him while trying to
do comedy. To be fair, that was that's a
first for everybody.
>> You You want You want this, pal?
>> Is that what you're saying?
>> Is that what you're saying? You want to
see me throw this back like one love? Is
that what you're saying?
>> I need more than that.
[cheering]
[screaming]
>> That's for you, big guy. That's for you.
>> None of you have been making eyes with
me the way he has all night. And that's
why he gets the goodies.
>> And you just see the face. My girlfriend
so mad right now. Look at her face. She
is pissed.
[laughter]
I'm getting I'm in trouble. [screaming]
I'm getting spanked tonight. That's for
sure. All right,
>> we got one more comic and then we're
going to call tonight. Guys, did you
have a good time so far tonight?
[applause]
>> I'm going to be walking around looking
for what who you think the comic of the
night is. We have it down to a
four-point list. It's on the chat chat.
Go ahead and voice your votes. I'm going
to walk around personally. your closing
comic tonight. Not the first time I've
shared a stage with this person, but the
first time I've seen them do comedy. Uh
dancer, right? Are you Were you a break
dancer?
>> You're not No. What was your vibe? What
were you doing again?
>> This is just the man. Just the man with
a microphone. Ladies and gentlemen, your
last performer tonight. Give it up FOR
THE FRESH MEAT ON STAGE. DWAYNE.
>> [cheering]
>> OKAY, y'all better hurry up and put pay
attention. Pay attention. First of all,
>> first of all, I'm going to talk to this
guy right here over there with the with
with the bun. With the bun, what his
name is.
>> Hey, hey, hey. Call your friend.
>> Ah, I don't know what you do, Hana, but
I don't know if to talk to you like
this.
>> What you do, Hana?
your shirt talk about uh talk about
Nigeria and you look like uh
>> you know what I'm saying? But anyway, uh
my name is Dwayne and uh this is the
first time. I'm just out here. I'm just
out here to vent.
>> I'm just out here to vent. Um
>> what his name is? Uh
Rampage.
>> Hey,
>> Rampage.
>> You I I know you and I know you already
um um uh what you call that? Uh
whatever you is. But uh anyway,
>> I I I am who I am. I am a local from
Hawaii, but I might might look like I'm
from wherever. New York, Chicago, or
whatever. But um I can do this. Hey,
hey, hey. Now,
>> what I look like?
>> Dominican. What? That's what I look
like, man. That's I look like I I look
like I'm
I'm the bad guy. You need somebody to
look like me like her cuz I'm the bad
guy, right?
>> You need somebody like me, right? That's
what you're talking about. But then I
can turn into the Filipino
because every time I come to PA, I need
to eat balloon, you know. And the
teacher's here and uh
the big one. [laughter]
I I am liking that one. I am liking that
one. When she sits when she sits like
this on the chair. Wait, hold on. Hold
on. When she when she sits like this on
the chair and she talks about her her
her big one. I am liking that one.
[laughter] I am liking that one. Because
because I am I am I I I am liking the
suzu. Me too. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> And you I'm not forgetting I'm not
forgetting about the teacher. The
teacher talks about the Do you know sign
language because you are so dramatic?
>> Yeah. You are so dramatic. You're here
with a microphone talking about
[laughter]
son of a [ __ ] Son of a [ __ ] And then
uh this guy over here with the tilted
brim. Hey, come
>> never mind him already. I'm talking to
you already.
I don't know if you stop early or or you
just quit or whatever, but do dirt.
Where's the J dirt? The Joe Dirt.
>> There you are, Joe Dirt. How are you
doing, Joe Dirt?
>> Hey, well, let me talk in your language.
This son of a [ __ ] going to come over
here and tell me like this. I'm telling
you right
ain't going to come up on this stage and
tell me about what the hell going on,
whatever going on with you, cuz I'm just
doing what I'm doing, copying you. But
this guy right here with the blue hat,
god damn it, man. You can see the future
with them glasses. You know what I'm
saying? You can see the future with them
glasses. I don't even know what you
said, but I remember what you said, but
I remember the hat.
>> I mean, you look like a you look like a
highlighter. One minute.
>> Chino. Chino. Hey, I love your thing.
This is my first time. I'm nervous as
[ __ ]
>> [cheering]
>> I I I I AM I I AM I'm nervous as [ __ ]
but um just because just because I'm a
local from Hawaii, I'm going to talk
like Uncle Dine. So, we in PA, right?
>> We in PA, right? Right. We in PA, right?
>> No, let me tell you like this. You
[ __ ] guys, you guys better go grab
the excuse my language,
>> but uh you better go grab on Lao right
now. One scoop rice. Grab one la and one
scoop rice right now. And go grab one.
Go mini stop and grab the mini stop
chicken.
>> Mini stop chicken and one beer. You
going to be all good. Go go go to Bin
Beach. Go look at the waves and all the
hippies. You guys going to be all right.
I'm telling you right now. You guys
going to be all right. Don't worry. Just
show.
Yeah. Yeah. Just show that. And then if
I if I look at if I look at
Like right
the looser it is the
>> n you got to go strong you got to go you
got the Filipino when you eat a when you
eat a balloon you all the Filipinos in
the house if you eat a balloon your man
is strong so you got to go strong shaka
yeah s yes sir yes you know already I
like your aloha shirt but return um
[laughter]
say I I'm not liking that one [ __ ] that
already chino GOD BLESS SALUTE
>> [cheering]
>> HEY, KEEP IT GOING FOR DWAYNE IN ALL THE
COMICS YOU heard tonight, ladies and
gentlemen. [applause]
He's the big puppy of Maui easily,
right? That dude could hit a four that
get that guy could hit a 450 homer for
sure. 110 excellent velocity. Come on
now.
I'm just talking ball now at this point.
It's funny. Uh, hey,
uh, real quick, I used to bounce bars in
Triangle back in the day, uh, at Tiki
Lounge, and I remember there's a group
of of Caribbean guys walking around.
>> And I saw a group of Hawaiian guys
interact, and I was like, "Oh, no. I
think they're going to fight and they're
interacting." I was like, "Oh, please
don't say anything racist, Hawaiian
guy." And he got close. He's like,
"That's right, bro.
>> This ain't the Caribbean, bro. You're on
the wrong island."
>> And I was like, "That that was educated
racism. That was a
Yeah, it's like Disney racism. That's
fine. That's fine. That floats. That was
hilarious. That was some pirates of pans
racism. We appreciate it.
>> All right, guys. We hope you had a good
time tonight. Make some noise for Bay
Coffee and Bar
[cheering] London Danny Kavika. Are you
K? Sorry. [applause] Lexa killing it
tonight. They've been wonderful to you.
Make sure you tip the [ __ ] out of them.
Comic of the night, earning a spot on
Joseé Raymond's show on Friday at the
playground. Jimbo slice, ladies and
gentlemen.
As voted by the room, as voted by the
internet, [applause] a clean sweep,
swept the leg. You got a fiveminut spot
on the big show this weekend.
>> Hey, make us proud. Do well. Eat your
waties. Um, audience members of the
night. It's been such a good audience. I
have two, three people I want to get.
>> Danny, do we have any sauce in the back?
>> Do we have any extra? No. Any sauce in
the back?
[laughter]
>> Like someone's like, who who'd rather a
shot? I got some. All right. All right.
All right.
>> All right. I heard you guys hot sauce,
right? You guys want hot sauce on here?
>> Center table.
>> Hot sauce.
>> I heard you. You're getting hot sauce,
right? We talked.
>> All right. I'm Hey, I'm getting a drink
for someone at this table cuz you guys
were awesome. I'm getting a drink for
someone at this table. Wait, no. Is Is
it last call already?
>> Did we do Did we do last call already?
>> You got We got Okay, we got one more
each for these people. One for over
here, one for over here on me if I if I
may. Thank you guys for being audience
members tonight. You guys were
fantastic. Thanks for giving and giving
and giving. I got a bottle of sauce for
you and I got a ball of sauce I'm going
to give to somebody else. Everybody have
a great night. We'll see you next week.
Well, what should next week's theme be?
Throw them at me. Throw them at me.
Who's got a theme for next week?
>> Theme for next week.
>> Now's your chance.
>> What was that?
>> A funny joke. Never. Never going to
happen.
>> Not on my watch. I'll I'll figure it
out. I'll be uncomfortable is fine. But
uh what was that?
>> Coffee.
>> I [laughter]
All right. Now, somebody definitely
needs to check check his Pornhub search
queue. [applause]
>> I know someone's got a lot of not mom,
not sister. Step.
Hey. Hey. Don't don't think you're bad.
Bashar was in here earlier and he's
like, "We [ __ ] marry our cousins,
dude. I don't give a shit." [laughter]
That's his That's his joke, not mine. I
repeat that. Double underline. All
right, guys. We hope you had a good
time. We'll see you next week. I'll tell
you what the theme is then. We love you.
Bye-bye. [cheering] End simulation. What
a great Monday. Over 75,000 views on
YouTube this week. Ho ho ho ho. Love you
guys. See you next time. Get home safe.
Bye-bye.
[laughter]
>> That's not true. All
right. You said you like it hotter,
right?
>> Ghost pepper, not scorpion.
>> I'll take it. I'll take it. But I WANT
[laughter]
>> NO, I Literally, this is fine.
Literally, no.
>> What's up, man?
I said he was off.
I need
somebody
knock out.
I did not.
>> I love you, Chad. I know you don't
believe me when I say this, but I have a
girlfriend to get home to, and I
literally can't afford to be single.
I gotta go. I love you.
Good job.
>> Thank you.
Let's
get
in my arm. Am I
>> said
again?
I saw it.
>> Here you go, birthday girl.
>> I'll be right there in a second. I
promise.
All right, chat. What is up? Thanks for
tuning in. You guys were awesome
tonight. On fire. Chair was goat. Chair,
I mean, I think Chair did more support
work than anybody else on stage today.
Um, definitely supported more than a
family, that's for sure. Jimbo is one of
the boys, chat. Yeah, Jimbo,
congratulations. He got set of the
night. He's going to be uh on the show
with Jose Raymond this Friday, September
4th, uh, at the playground if you're on
Maui. If you have the chance to see it,
what we got here? That's some good work.
Chair, I know if chair, we can't include
chair in the poll because you will
always vote for chair. We got to keep it
special. We don't want to burn you out
on the chair. We know if we give you all
the chair you've ever wanted, you would
OD on the chair and then you would want
the chair no longer. So, we can't do
that to you. What we got here, Chino,
you need to start selling autograph 3D.
Dude, that's not a bad idea. I should
start 3D printing chairs as little
keychains and just sell those as our
logo. I [ __ ] love that.
>> Hey, thanks Jimbo. You're the go,
brother. Appreciate W chair. Uh, hey, I
want to give a shout out to a commenter.
Uh, I think it was uh comrad
not canrad something like that. Uh,
every time I come on screen they just
type in blazian blazian blazian. And
that happened for like months and then
they stopped commenting and then they
came back today and they said blazian
but you look good bro. Hilarious. I love
the inside jokes. I get it. I'm here
with you guys. I [ __ ] love it. Uh,
what we got here?
>> Chair burn. We raise so much money. Hey,
you know what? Yeah, if we ever do need
to raise some money for like something,
we'll do a chair raiser. Oh, thank you
so much. See, look. I do get paid a
little bit of money. Not much, but
something. It's enough to feed feed the
guest tank a little bit. What did Joe
say about Jimbo? Chair is awesome.
A vote for the chair is a vote for
Jimbo. Hilarious. Yes, it truly is. the
percentages really do come out. Um, oh,
thanks for all the love on the H shirt,
by the way. Uh, I'll be honest, I wore
this and I thought you guys were going
to eat me alive, chat. I thought you
guys were going to be like, "What this?
What the [ __ ] is that stupid?" I'm so
glad that you have the same taste in
clothing that I do cuz I really do love
this shirt. And uh I'm happy that you
like it, too. Gajun, too. Yes, JFK. Gian
also works. Um, but he got to it first,
so that's his bit. Uh, that's me and his
bit. Uh, you need to clear the chain
after. Yeah, I think we do. I think I
still see a spot on it.
Little little little trail web. So, you
need to make a chair part of your logo.
Yeah, I agree. We're going to make a we
are going to make the chair the logo
pretty soon. That's a really good idea.
We had already said that last week. I
think SDL loves the shirt. Hey, thanks.
Appreciate you. Thanks for tuning in
again. This is what, like three weeks in
a row I seen you here. Appreciate that.
Know you've been on for more, but in a
row. Appreciate you.
No, because you're not embarrassing
yourself like the like the comedians. A
come on. I embarrassed myself plenty. Uh
I've just been doing it. I've just been
embarrassing myself longer. Uh so I know
how to do it with some dignity, but not
much. T-shirt go to JFK. Appreciate you.
Accept the chair as your Lord and
Savior. Dang, Allison, you're starting
to start a whole cult. I appreciate the
levels there. Clanker humor shirt. Oh.
Oh, you think this is like AI? Yeah, it
probably is an AI made shirt. Um, but
you know it's better than AI made shirt
than made by Chinese children. What do
you have to say about that? Would you
rather have child labor t-shirts than
robot made? Why is that? You'd rather
have children suffering than letting
automatic things make your clothing?
That's a pretty weird No, I'm just
joking. Uh, [laughter]
that's that's just the power of momentum
that I was using on you there. Um,
>> the chair does not approve of the shirt.
Uh, you know, the chair and the shirt
cannot exist simultaneously. I agree.
Either a chair or shirt must go. Oh, I
thought that was a fight. That was just
a drunk. Uh,
>> Chino embarrassing himself with grace.
Every single day, Henry. Every single
day. Um, you know, if you're if you're
not disappointing somebody, then you're
not trying hard enough. Uh, what do you
think when the cats see the bowl of
milk? Do you think they lick it up? Lick
it up.
I I will always get a kiss reference. I
will never leave you hanging there. What
was that? Jim,
>> if that's your real name. [laughter]
>> I want the chair labor. Yeah, we got to
get We got to get the chair labor. The
child labor tees, too. I want child
labor. That should be another one of our
merchandise. We just have a shirt that
says child labor. Um, that chair needs
chery. Cherrapy. Ah, good pun there.
All right, we're going to be wrapping
this up pretty soon. They just started
playing Ace of Bass, which means that
we're about to get copyrighted if we
don't. end soon. Um, thank you so much
for joining us. Check out my buddy Jose
Raymond on social media. Um, if you if
you can't check out his show, if you
can't, just give him a follow. Uh,
Raymond, come on in here real quick.
>> All right. What's up, everybody?
>> Yeah. What's up?
>> Say what's up to the audience.
>> Hey, what's up? How you doing?
>> Jose Raymond, comedian on Instagram.
>> Follow Chino. I'm at his friend page.
>> Hell yeah.
>> Jose's an OG, man. We've been working
together a long time back and forth. Uh
he's been killing it on the mainland for
a while too. Uh amongst the LA comedy
scene. He's done the road stuff, dude.
>> We're going to uh LA Pasadena Ice House
in Pasadena.
>> Pasina. Yeah.
>> On the 6th with Tommy Davidson. Uh Lat
Factory September 27th.
>> There you go. So if you're LA, now you
know where to see him. Check him out.
Jose Raymond.
>> Hey, say hi to Annabelle for me.
>> Oh, shout out to Annabelle. That that's
from Jose. Make sure you know. Uh thank
you guys for checking in.
got a ticket to Africa for me. Oh,
wonderful. Uh, I've always wanted to go.
Can't wait. Uh, let's see what we got
here. Do you do a set myself somewhere
else? Yes, I do. If you look in our
previous live streams, uh, in I think it
was July, I did a full hour set. It's
nothing special. It's filmed from a
phone. But if you want to see some more
of my comedy, I will be filming a
special soon, sometime end of this year.
Uh, hopefully we can get that out to
you. and uh so that you can see more and
then you guys can do what you do in the
chat on my video and make a boy feel
special. Um, numchuck skills. Love it.
>> Vote for Pedro,
>> man.
>> Yeah, I guess you're Pedro, dude. At
first I was like,
>> [ __ ] I HEARD THAT A LOT of
times. Yeah, Pedro, [ __ ]
>> At first I was like, what's this vote
for Pedro [ __ ] And I was like, oh, oh,
I get it.
>> What does he say? I ain't really watch
this [ __ ]
>> They just told me that I look like Pedro
before.
>> I I was really hot. I was really [ __ ]
that
>> that's close enough.
>> That's why I don't act cuz they asked me
to speak like that. I don't really do
that [ __ ]
>> dude. We need to show you some Napoleon
Dynamite. He would not sit through it.
He'd be like, "This movie is stupid as
[ __ ] I guarantee it. I guarantee it."
Guys, thanks for tuning in. We'll see
you next week. Thanks for supporting the
Comedy Simulator. Uh, please like,
subscribe, do all those things if you
hadn't yet. We had over 80K viewers
tonight. You guys are awesome. Thanks
for making this so much fun. Otherwise,
this is just an open mic on an island in
the middle of the ocean, but you guys
make this so much more fun. Uh, shout
out to Australia, shout out to England,
shout out to the East Coast, man. I know
you guys are watching. I'm looking at
the demographics. Uh, thank you so much
for tuning in. I hope it makes your
Mondays a little bit better. Uh, have a
great night. We'll see you next week. If
you got anything to say, say it now so I
can read it later. Love you. Bye.